While you and Charlie have been working on the main loop,
أثناء ما تعملون مع تشارلي في التكرار الحلقي الرئيسي،
I've been working on the find_first_link function.
أعمل على دالة find_first_link.
This collaboration wouldn't be possible if we hadn't planned things out ahead
لن يكون هذا التعاون ممكنًا في حالة عدم التخطيط للأمور في وقت مبكر
of time and broken the crawler down into smaller parts.
ونحوِّل المتتبع إلى أجزاء صغيرة.
Beyond that though, Charlie had to specify
وما هو أكثر من ذلك هو أن تشارلي كان عليها تحديد
how her code would use the find_first_link function.
كيف سيستخدم كودها دالة find_first_link.
Charlie will call the function by passing in a string.
ستستدعي تشارلي الدالة عن طريق التمرير في سلسلة.
I don't know what variable names Charlie defined in her part of the program,
لا أعرف أسماء المتغيرات التي حددتها تشارلي في الجزء الخاص بها من البرنامج،
so I'll just refer to this function's input as url.
لذلك سأشير فقط إلى إدخال هذه الدالة كعنوان url.
The function does its work and returns another string.
تؤدي الدالة عملها وتقوم بإرجاع سلسلة أخرى.
The return value is the first link from the article that was passed into the function.
قيمة الإرجاع هي أول رابط من المقالة التي تم تمريرها إلى الدالة.
This specification is like a contract between Charlie and me.
تشبه هذه المواصفات توقيع عقد بيني وبين تشارلي.
If her code provides the correct argument and my code returns the correct result,
إذا كان كودها يوفر الوسيطة الصحيحة ويرجع كودي النتيجة الصحيحة،
then our program will work correctly.
فسيعمل برنامجنا بشكل صحيح.
Likewise, I can implement the function however I like and Charlie doesn't have to
وبالمثل، يمكنني تنفيذ الدالة بالطريقة التي أفضلها كما يجب ألا ينتاب تشارلي
worry about how it'll fit into her code because we've
القلق بشأن كيفية ملاءمتها لكودها لأننا
already agreed on how her code will call the function.
متفقين بالفعل في طريقة استدعاء كودها للدالة.